[
  {
    "name": "Atom",
    "key": 1,
    "chapters": [
      {
        "name": "Text Editing I",
        "key": 1,
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Cut to End of Line",
            "answer": "⌃K"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Delete to Beginning of Word",
            "answer": "⌥BACKSPACE"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Delete to End of Word",
            "answer": "⌥D"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Delete Line",
            "answer": "⇧⌃K"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Duplicate Line",
            "answer": "⇧⌘D"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Go to Line",
            "answer": "⌃G"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 2,
        "name": "Text Editing II",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Go to Matching Bracket",
            "answer": "⌃M"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Indent Selected Text",
            "answer": "⌘]"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Outdent Selected Text",
            "answer": "⌘["
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Join Lines",
            "answer": "⌘J"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Move to Beginning of Word",
            "answer": "⌥B"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Move to End of Word",
            "answer": "⌥F"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 3,
        "name": "Code Navigation I",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Move to Beginning of Line",
            "answer": "⌃A"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Move to End of Line",
            "answer": "⌃E"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Move Line Up",
            "answer": "⌃⌘UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Move Line Down",
            "answer": "⌃⌘DOWN"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Move to Top of File",
            "answer": "⌘UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Move to Bottom of File",
            "answer": "⌘Down"
          },
          {
            "key": 7,
            "question": "Move to First Character of Line",
            "answer": "⌃A"
          },
          {
            "key": 8,
            "question": "Move to Last Character of Line",
            "answer": "⌃E"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 4,
        "name": "Code Selection I",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Select Left Character",
            "answer": "⇧⌃B"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Select Rigth Character",
            "answer": "⇧⌃F"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Select to Beginning of Word",
            "answer": "⇧⌥B"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Select to End of Word",
            "answer": "⇧⌥F"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Select Entire Word",
            "answer": "⇧⌃W"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 5,
        "name": "Code Selection II",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Select to First Character of Line",
            "answer": "⇧⌘LEFT"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Select to Last Character of Line",
            "answer": "⇧⌘RIGHT"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Select to Same Position, Next Line",
            "answer": "⇧DOWN"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Select to Same Postion, Previous Line",
            "answer": "⇧UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Select to Top of File",
            "answer": "⇧⌘UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Select to Bottom of File",
            "answer": "⇧⌘DOWN"
          },
          {
            "key": 7,
            "question": "Select Next",
            "answer": "⌘D"
          },
          {
            "key": 8,
            "question": "Select Line",
            "answer": "⌘L"
          },
          {
            "key": 9,
            "question": "Toggle Line Comments",
            "answer": "⌘"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 6,
        "name": "Code Folding",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Fold Code",
            "answer": "⌥⌘["
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Unfold Code",
            "answer": "⌥⌘]"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Fold Selected Text",
            "answer": "⌥⌃⌘F"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 7,
        "name": "Bookmarks",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Toggle Bookmark",
            "answer": "⌘F2"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "View All Bookmarks",
            "answer": "⌃F2"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Jump to Next Bookmark",
            "answer": "F2"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Jump to Previous Bookmark",
            "answer": "⇧F2"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Clear All Bookmarks",
            "answer": "⇧⌘F2"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 8,
        "name": "Editor View / Files",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Split Panes Vertically",
            "answer": "⌘K DOWN"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Split Panes Horizontally",
            "answer": "⌘K RIGHT"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Vertical Navigation Panes",
            "answer": "⌘K ⌘DOWN"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Horizontal Navigation Panes",
            "answer": "⌘K ⌘RIGHT"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Toggle Full Screen",
            "answer": "⌃⌘F"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Toggle Tree View",
            "answer": "⌘\\"
          },
          {
            "key": 7,
            "question": "Find Open File",
            "answer": "⌘B"
          },
          {
            "key": 8,
            "question": "Find Modified, Untracked (git) File",
            "answer": "⇧⌘B"
          },
          {
            "key": 9,
            "question": "Open Tree View",
            "answer": "⌃O"
          },
          {
            "key": 10,
            "question": "Add a File",
            "answer": "A"
          },
          {
            "key": 11,
            "question": "Move a File",
            "answer": "M"
          },
          {
            "key": 12,
            "question": "Delete a File",
            "answer": "DELETE"
          },
          {
            "key": 13,
            "question": "Reopen Last File",
            "answer": "⇧⌘T"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 9,
        "name": "Find & Repalace",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Find String in Current File",
            "answer": "⌘F"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Find String in All Project Files",
            "answer": "⇧⌘F"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Find Next Matching String",
            "answer": "⌘G"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Find Previous Matching String",
            "answer": "⇧⌘G"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Select Next Matching String",
            "answer": "⌘D"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Select All Matching String",
            "answer": "⌃⌘G"
          },
          {
            "key": 7,
            "question": "Replace String in Current File",
            "answer": "⌥⌘F"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 10,
        "name": "Misc.",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Open Command Palette",
            "answer": "⇧⌘P"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Open Configuration Editor",
            "answer": "⌘,"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Toggle Autocomplete",
            "answer": "⌃SPACE"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Find Matching Bracket",
            "answer": "⌃M"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "key": 2,
    "name": "Sublime Text3",
    "chapters": [
      {
        "key": 1,
        "name": "Text Editing Beginner",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Move line/selection up",
            "answer": "⌃⌘UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Cut line",
            "answer": "⌘X"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Insert line after",
            "answer": "⌘↵"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Insert line before",
            "answer": "⇧⌘↵"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Move line/selection down",
            "answer": "⌃⌘DOWN"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Select word",
            "answer": "⌘D"
          },
          {
            "key": 7,
            "question": "Go to matching parentheses",
            "answer": "⌃M"
          },
          {
            "key": 8,
            "question": "Select all contents of the current",
            "answer": "⇧⌃M"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 2,
        "name": "Text Editing Intermediate",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Indent current line(s)",
            "answer": "⌘]"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Un-indent current line(s)",
            "answer": "⌘["
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Duplicate line(s)",
            "answer": "⇧⌘D"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Comment/un-comment current line",
            "answer": "⌘/"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Block comment current selection",
            "answer": "⌥⌘/"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Redo",
            "answer": "⌘Y"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 3,
        "name": "Text Editing Intermediate II",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "Delete from cursor to end of line",
            "answer": "⌘K ⌘K"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "Insert line after",
            "answer": "⌘K BACKSPACE"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "Paste and indent correctly",
            "answer": "⇧⌘V"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "Select next auto-complete suggestion",
            "answer": "⌃ SPACE"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "Soft undo",
            "answer": "⌘U"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "Paste from history",
            "answer": "⌥⌘V"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "key": 3,
    "name": "WebStorm",
    "chapters": [
      {
        "key": 1,
        "name": "查找和删除",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "在当前文件中查找",
            "answer": "⌘G"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "在某个文件夹内查找",
            "answer": "⌘⇧F"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "替换",
            "answer": "⌘R"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "删除行",
            "answer": "⌘BACKSPACE"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "高级重命名",
            "answer": "⇧F6"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 2,
        "name": "选择",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "复制行",
            "answer": "⌘D"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "剪切行",
            "answer": "⌘X"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "选中多相同单词，一起修改",
            "answer": "⌃G"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "向上移动选中代码块",
            "answer": "⌘⇧UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "向下移动选中代码块",
            "answer": "⌘⇧DOWN"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "增加代码块选择",
            "answer": "⌥UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 7,
            "question": "缩小代码块选择",
            "answer": "⌥DOWN"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 3,
        "name": "导航",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "选择最近打开的文件",
            "answer": "⌘E"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "跳转到定义",
            "answer": "⌘B"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "显示快捷目录",
            "answer": "⌘UP"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "复制文件当前路径",
            "answer": "⌘⇧C"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 4,
        "name": "标签页",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "切换上一个标签",
            "answer": "⌘⇧["
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "切换下一个标签",
            "answer": "⌘⇧]"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "合并下一行",
            "answer": "⌃⇧J"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 5,
        "name": "显示",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "折叠代码块",
            "answer": "⌘-"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "展开折叠代码块",
            "answer": "⌘+"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "折叠所有代码块",
            "answer": "⌘⇧-"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "展开所有代码块",
            "answer": "⌘⇧+"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "折叠展开选中代码块",
            "answer": "⌘."
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "显示参数信息",
            "answer": "⌘P"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "key": 4,
    "name": "Iterm2",
    "chapters": [
      {
        "key": 1,
        "name": "标签",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "新建标签",
            "answer": "⌘T"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "关闭标签",
            "answer": "⌘W"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "切换上一个标签",
            "answer": "⌘LEFT"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "切换下一个标签",
            "answer": "⌘RIGHT"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "切换到第3个标签",
            "answer": "⌘3"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 2,
        "name": "屏幕",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "垂直分屏",
            "answer": "⌘D"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "切换上一个屏幕",
            "answer": "⌘⌥LEFT"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "切换下一个屏幕",
            "answer": "⌘⌥RIGHT"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "清屏",
            "answer": "⌘R"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "切换全屏",
            "answer": "⌘↵"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 3,
        "name": "历史",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "查看历史命令",
            "answer": "⌘;"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "上一个命令",
            "answer": "⌃P"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "下一个命令",
            "answer": "⌃N"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 4,
        "name": "删除",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "清除当前行",
            "answer": "⌃U"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "删除光标到行尾",
            "answer": "⌃K"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "删除光标到行首",
            "answer": "⌃W"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "删除当前光标字符",
            "answer": "⌃D"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "删除光标前的字符",
            "answer": "⌃H"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "key": 4,
        "name": "编辑",
        "items": [
          {
            "key": 1,
            "question": "光标移到行尾",
            "answer": "⌃E"
          },
          {
            "key": 2,
            "question": "光标移到行首",
            "answer": "⌃A"
          },
          {
            "key": 3,
            "question": "光标前进",
            "answer": "⌃F"
          },
          {
            "key": 4,
            "question": "光标后退",
            "answer": "⌃B"
          },
          {
            "key": 5,
            "question": "光标后移一个单词",
            "answer": "⌥F"
          },
          {
            "key": 6,
            "question": "光标前移一个单词",
            "answer": "⌥B"
          },
          {
            "key": 7,
            "question": "交换光标文本",
            "answer": "⌃T"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]
